

# Rodriguez Agustin

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate professional with a background in administration. With 5 years of experience in the administrative field, I have developed skills in organization of equipment and personnel management. My focus is always on continuos imrpovement.

Additionally I have a deep interest in programming, with experience in Python and c++. I love solving problems complex and develop innovativa solutions.

### **HABILITIES**

- Problem solving
- Office package domain
- Teamwork
- Programming in Python and C++

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ADMINISTRATIVE AUXILIAR**

"Policia de la Ciudad" (May 2019 - Actually)

- Management of Office Package
- Management of Institutional Computer Systems
- Public Attetiont

#### **INSTALLER TECHNICIAN**

"FullSat S.R.L" (January 2019 - May 2019)

- Internet Installation
- Costumer Service
- Technicial Support

## **FORMATION**

#### PROGRAMMING TECHNICIAN

"Universidad Tecnologica Nacional" (2024 - actually)

#### **ELECTRONICAL TECHNICIAN**

""E.E.S.T.N°9 - LANUS" (2011 - 2017)

## LANGUAGES

SPANISH Native
ENGLISH Advanced (C1)